

### CONTACT

Email:

ana.khomasuridze.2@iliauni.edu.ge

Phone Number:

555 44 04 88

Address:

Tbilisi, Vazisubani 2nd district

GitHub:

https://github.com/Khomas5

### **SKILLS**

- HTML5
- CSS3
- SCSS
- JavaScript
- Git/GitHub
- Bootstrap

## **LANGUAGES**

- Georgian Native
- English B2/C1
- Russian Beginner, A1 A2
- Arabic Beginner, A2

# ANA KHOMASURIDZE

Junior Front-End Developer

I started studying front-end web programming at the beginning of 2022 when I took a 6-month course where, in addition to HTML, CSS, and JS, I learned the basics of Angular. In the same period, I participated in the Women Tech Hub project of Ilia State University funded by the British Council, where I received both theoretical and practical trainings in the direction of WEB development. I also took Udemy courses in advanced CSS and SCSS, and currently, I'm taking a Javascript and React course. From October 2022, I am working as an intern at the Ascended startup company, where I do real projects, try to learn more and gain experience.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR FRONT-END 10.2022 - present DEVELOPER INTERN

Ascended

WAITRESS 07.2021 - 11.2021

Stamba Hotel

CASHIER-CONSULTANT 12.2019-10.2020

KFC

WAITRESS 06.2018-09.2018

Lopota Spa Resort

## **EDUCATION**

IT Step Academy 01,2022-07,2022

FRONT-END Web-Programming

Ilia State University 09.2020 - present

Bachelor of Social Sciences

## PROJECTS AND ACTIVITIES

Woman Tech-Hub project 03.22-07.2022 participant in Web development

Ilia State UniMember of the Diplomacy Department of Student Unity of Georgia

03.22-06.2022